myleadcompany.com 2017-12-31

# MyLeadCompany.com - network marketing & mlm leads

 | marketing associate

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. We recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of the personal information we learn about you while you visit our web site. This privacy policy lets you know how we will use and protect that information. The information that we receive depends on what you do during your visit, and what service(s) you request.

* * *

1\. NON-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION.   
We may collect information about our members, sales, traffic patterns and related site information. This information helps us evaluate and improve our site and is sometimes useful for marketing analysis. 

2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION.   
When you request a service or information, place an order, submit feedback or participate in a blog, forum or survey, we may need to ask you for personal information such as your name, address, email address and telephone number. If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you cannot access the member area. 

3\. USE OF "COOKIES."   
Cookies are small files Web sites place on your hard drive that allow sites to identify you. The use of cookies is a common practice on many Web sites. For example, if you allow a site to remember your login name or password, the site places a cookie on your computer. Cookies cannot read any other information on your hard drive. We may place cookies on your computer to allow us to identify you. We may use cookies to measure Web traffic, to offer you certain services and to customize your visit. However, if you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, your browser may permit you to do so. 

4\. SECURITY.   
MyLeadCompany.com has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers. 

5\. LINKED SITES.   
Our site is linked to other sites. We cannot be held responsible for the privacy or security practices of any other Web sites. They are separate entities. 

6\. CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY.   
We reserve the right to change this policy at any time without notice.
